Huh?
あれ?
I'm really grinning.
めっちゃニヤね
I'm really smiling.
めっちゃニヤじゃん
I'm grinning.
ニヤニヤしちゃう
You're your own guy.
あんた自分のやつだね
He came to sleep.
寝てきてくれた
Did you sleep?
寝てくれたの?
Pull me out of the house.
家から引っ張って
I can see it.
見えちゃう
You can see it.
見えちゃうね
Dangerous, dangerous.
危ない危ない
What were you doing today?
今日何してたの?
I went to eat at a cafe today.
今日はカフェにご飯食べて
What did you eat?
何食べたの?
pasta.
パスタ
pasta?
パスタ?
Were you eating pasta wearing this outfit?
この服着てパスタ食ってたの?
Oh, this is how you came?
あ、これで来たの?
different.
違う
No, no.
違う違う
different?
違う?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうだ
Just smell it.
一応匂い嗅いで
Oh, no, no.
あ、ダメダメ
You might be sweating a lot.
めっちゃ汗かいてるかもしれない
I'm sweating so much.
めっちゃ汗かいてる
No, no, no.
ダメダメ
I was walking all day today.
今日一日歩いてたから
Second-rate.
次
Huh?
あれ?
a little bit...
ちょっと...
Is it something white?
なんか 白いのかな?
Huh?
あれ?
Is it pink?
ピンク色かな?
It's a skirt for show.
見せるためのスカートじゃん
No, no, no.
違う違う違う
different?
違う?
It looks stupid.
モロ見えだ
モロ見えだね
You'll get used to it.
慣れちゃう
That's fine, right?
いい でしょ
Are you touching it?
触ってるのかよ
Yeah.
うん
different.
違う
Huh?
あれ?
I can see it.
見えちゃう
This is how I feel.
こういう気分だね
The contents.
中身が
I can't see it.
見えないやん
I can see it.
見えちゃう
見 えちゃう
Ah, amazing.
あーすごい
By train or something.
電車とかでさ
You can see it.
見えちゃうじゃん
I was carrying it on my back.
背負ってた
Too scary.
怖すぎる
Too scary?
怖すぎる?
I can see it.
見 えてる
You're being watched.
見られてるよね
Yeah.
うん
Oh no.
やば
Too cute.
可愛すぎる
The viewers were watching.
視聴者視聴者見られてた
Ah hello.
あーヘロー
It's heroic.
ヘローイね
Kiss.
キス
What happened?
何になっちゃった?
amazing
すごい
hey.
ね
It's really standing up.
め っちゃ立ってる
Are you really standing up?
めっちゃ立ってる?
I think I'll just go with that.
もうそれだけで行っちゃいそうかな
No.
ダメ
Ah, amazing.
あーすごい
It was really tingling.
めっちゃうずいになったね
It's dangerous though.
やばいんだけど
It feels so good.
め っちゃ気持ちいい
That's amazing.
すごいね
Ah, amazing.
あーすごい
Amazing amazing.
すごい すごい
Once again, I turned around a little and reached out.
もう一回ちょっと後ろ向いて手ついて
I can see it.
見えちゃったね
Don't hide it for a second.
ちょっと隠さないで
Look here.
こっち見て
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
I didn't take a picture.
撮ってないよ
I didn't take any pictures.
全然撮ってないよ
This way?
こっち?
Yeah.
うん
I feel like it looks nice.
眺めいいなって感じ
I'm taking pictures.
撮ってるな
Did you find out?
バレた?
It suits you.
似合うね
whole body.
全身
nice.
いいね
Of these.
こっちのうち
I don't need it anymore.
もういらないね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
大丈夫か
Oh no.
やば
It came out.
出てきた
Did you hide it?
隠しちゃったの?
It's my own hands.
自分の両手です
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
It's close.
近いよ
Roundness.
丸み
Isn't it very close?
めっちゃ近いんじゃない?
Go, go, go.
行く行く
delicious.
美味しい
It feels good there.
そこ気持ちいい
So-so.
そこそこ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Go, go, go.
行く行く
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I'm sleeping a lot.
すっごい寝てる
cute.
可愛い
It's such a beautiful red.
すっごい綺麗な赤いし
It hurts.
痛いな
Won't you let me go?
離してくれない?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I'm going.
行っちゃう
Oh no.
や だ
It's just no good.
ダメというだけだよ
I'll go there.
そこで行っちゃう
I'm going.
行っちゃう
Just lick it a lot.
いっぱい舐めてやるだけだよ
Feel good.
気持ちよく
It feels good to lick it.
気持ちよく舐めちゃうね
It's the whole thing.
全体だね
That's a good thing.
いいことだよ
Let me show you how it works.
ちょっと操作見せて
fault.
あら
It's so cute.
めちゃめちゃ可愛い
Thank you for waiting one more time.
もう一回、もう一回お待たせ
It's going to be delicious.
美味しくなっちゃう
I want a big one.
大きいの欲しい
No, I won't say it anymore.
いやー、もう言わない
Too good.
上手すぎる
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's scary here.
やばいね、ここ
Ah, it feels good.
あー、気持ちいい
That's amazing though.
すごいんだけど
Please wait a moment.
ちょっとお待ちして
Look with your mouth.
口で見て
terrible.
やばい
Wait a minute, I'll go.
ちょっと待って、行っちゃうよ
Yeah yeah yeah.
うんうんうん
Wait a minute, I can't go.
ちょっと待って、行けない
want?
欲しい?
want.
欲しい
That's fine, right?
いいでしょ
My hips are moving.
腰動いてる
Yeah yeah.
うんうん
It's so delicious.
めっちゃ美味しい
Is it really delicious?
めっちゃ美味しい?
Yeah.
うん
What do you call this?
これ、なんて言うの?
Yeah.
うん
I want you to eat my dick.
ちんちんを食べて欲しい
Penis?
ちんちんを?
Yeah.
うん
Where do you see dick?
ちんちんをどこ見るの?
up.
うえ
Something.
なんか
Something?
なんか?
What do you say?
なんて言うの?
Where do you see dick?
ちんちんをどこ見るの?
Ah, it feels good.
あー、気持ちいい
Oh, no.
あー、ダメ
Just put it in and go.
入れただけで行っちゃう
Oh, wow, I was so excited.
あー、すごい、ビカビカした
Just put it in and go.
入れただけで行っちゃう
Ah, it feels good.
あー、気持ちいい
It's really closed.
すっごい閉まってる
Ah, it feels good.
あー、気持ちいい
go?
行く?
Are you leaving already?
もう行っちゃうの?
Yeah, I'm leaving now.
うん、もう行っちゃう
Ah, ah, let's go.
あ、あ、行く行く
It's soooo tight.
すっげーきつい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It feels so good.
すっげー気持ちいい
Oh no.
やば
amazing.
すごい
a,
あ、
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
amazing.
すごい
terrible.
やばい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Ah, let's go.
あ、行く
amazing
すごい
hey.
ね
I'll mix it up.
混 ぜていっちゃう
dangerous.
危ない
Go, go, go.
行く行く
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Messed up.
めちゃめちゃ
amazing.
すごい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Go, go, go.
行く行く
Feels good.
気持ちいい
air
気
It lasts a long time.
持 ちいい
go
行く
go.
行 く
行く
Go, go, go.
行く行く
Amazing view.
すごい眺める
It's jiggling.
プルプルしてる
Put it on your feet.
足上にあげて
It feels so good.
すっげー気持ちいい
terrible.
やばい
I think I'll try a few things.
ちょっといろいろやってみようかな
Ai-chan?
あいちゃん?
Go, go, go.
行く行く行く
Just a little bit.
ちょっとちょっと
Please come and have a look.
一旦ちょっと来てみてさ
Come and try it.
来てみて
That's amazing.
すごいね
terrible.
やばい
Ah, it's out.
あ、出ちゃった
That's amazing, isn't it?
すごいでしょ
It came out the moment I pulled it out.
抜いた瞬間今出ちゃったね
a little bit.
ちょっと
sorry.
ごめんなさい
The uniform caught my eye.
制服に目がかかっちゃった
Too big for Mari.
マリには偉すぎて
But there's something I want to do.
でもちょっとやりたいことあるからさ
Go back and back.
後ろへ行って後ろ
still.
まだ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
amazing.
すごい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Go, go, go.
行く行く
Feels good.
気持ちいい
amazing.
すごい
terrible.
やばい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
amazing.
すごい
It's already here.
もうこのうちだって
Did you do it?
してました?
Did it come out?
出ちゃった?
Were you playing out the window?
窓ぼうでしてたの?
Yeah.
うん
I put it out.
出 しちゃったよ
I went to a strange place.
変なところで行っちゃったわ